export const quizData = {
    categories: [
      {
        id: "js_basics",
        name: "JavaScript Basics",
        questions: [
          {
            id: "q1",
            question: "What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called 'script.js'?",
            options: [
              "A. <script name='script.js'>",
              "B. <script href='script.js'>",
              "C. <script src='script.js'>",
              "D. <script file='script.js'>"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "C",
            timeLimit: 10
          },
          {
            id: "q2",
            question: "Which company developed JavaScript?",
            options: [
              "A. Microsoft",
              "B. Netscape",
              "C. Google",
              "D. Mozilla"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "B",
            timeLimit: 10
          },
          {
            id: "q3",
            question: "What is JSX?",
            options: [
              "A. HTML",
              "B. JavaScript",
              "C. JavaScript XML",
              "D. XML"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "C",
            timeLimit: 10
          },
          {
            id: "q4",
            question: "useState use",
            options: [
              "A. Store data globally",
              "B. Store data locally",
              "C. Store data inside local storage",
              "D. Pass data to child"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "B",
            timeLimit: 10
          },
          {
            id: "q5",
            question: "The 'function' and ' var' are known as",
            options: [
              "A. Keywords",
              "B. Data types",
              "C. Prototypes",
              "D. Declaration "
            ],
            correctAnswer: "D",
            timeLimit: 10
          },
        ]
      },
      {
        id: "react_basics",
        name: "React JS Basics",
        questions: [
          {
            id: "q1",
            question: "What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called 'script.js'?",
            options: [
              "A. <script name='script.js'>",
              "B. <script href='script.js'>",
              "C. <script src='script.js'>",
              "D. <script file='script.js'>"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "C",
            timeLimit: 10
          },
          {
            id: "q2",
            question: "Which company developed JavaScript?",
            options: [
              "A. Microsoft",
              "B. Netscape",
              "C. Google",
              "D. Mozilla"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "B",
            timeLimit: 10
          },
          {
            id: "q3",
            question: "What is JSX?",
            options: [
              "A. HTML",
              "B. JavaScript",
              "C. JavaScript XML",
              "D. XML"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "C",
            timeLimit: 10
          },
          {
            id: "q4",
            question: "useState use",
            options: [
              "A. Store data globally",
              "B. Store data locally",
              "C. Store data inside local storage",
              "D. Pass data to child"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "B",
            timeLimit: 10
          },
          {
            id: "q5",
            question: "The 'function' and ' var' are known as",
            options: [
              "A. Keywords",
              "B. Data types",
              "C. Prototypes",
              "D. Declaration "
            ],
            correctAnswer: "D",
            timeLimit: 10
          },
        ]
      }
    ]
  };